Hilary Knight Papers 1992.0047
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
Hilary Knight Papers
1956-2001
1992.0047
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
17.5 Linear feet
Hilary Knight is a New York-based illustrator for children's books and magazines. This collection contains preliminary and finished artwork, manuscripts, galleys, proofs, and dummies pertaining to 30 of the illustrator's published books and numerous published articles.
Knight, Hilary
Scope and Contents
This collection contains preliminary and finished artwork, manuscripts, galleys, proofs, and dummies pertaining to thirty of the illustrator's published books and numerous published articles. This collection also includes many signed and dated explanatory notes from Mr. Knight, added to the collection before it was donated to the University of Connecticut in 2001.
Custodial History
Donated to the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center by Hilary Knight in 2001.
Arrangement
Series I: Correspondence and Notes (undated, 1960-2001)
Series II: Published Books Illustrated by Hilary Knight (1956-2000)
Series III: Published Articles Illustrated by Hilary Knight (1973-1997)
Series IV: Unpublished Works (undated)
Series V: Promotional Materials (1976-1995)
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to children's literature and associated artwork. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Bibliography
Evans, Dilys. "Hilary Knight, A Natural Born Rascal" in Show & Tell: Exploring the Fine Art of Children's Book Illustration. San Francisco: Chronicle Books, 2008: p. 10-21 "Meet the Authors: Hilary Knight," Barnes and Noble,(November 11, 2011) http://www.barnesandnoble.com/writers/writerdetails.asp?z=y&cid=840202#bio
Biography
Hilary Knight was born November 1, 1926 in Hempstead, Long Island. His mother, Katherine Sturges, was a successful commercial and fashion illustrator, known for her graceful Oriental-style artwork. His father, Clayton Knight, was a popular aviation book illustrator. Both parents were extremely influential in Mr. Knight’s decision to pursue a career in illustration, and his mother’s love of traditional Asian art is often exhibited in Mr. Knight’s own artwork. At the age of sixteen, he enrolled in the Art Students League in New York City to study art. While there, he gained a reputation as a high-spirited, somewhat mischievous student. In 1944, at the age of eighteen, Mr. Knight dropped out of school and joined the United States Navy, where he served as a ship painter for eighteen months during the height of the World War II. Following his time in the Navy, Mr. Knight worked short stints as a set designer and magazine illustrator, where he became known for his whimsical black line style of drawing. Mr. Knight began illustrating children’s books for the Mrs. Piggle-Wiggle Series by Betty MacDonald in the 1940s, but a fateful meeting with singer Kay Thompson at the Plaza Hotel in New York really launched Mr. Knight’s career as a children’s book illustrator. Following the publication of Eloise in 1955, Mr. Knight went on to illustrate over fifty books and numerous magazine articles for children.
Mr. Knight’s illustrations are known for their whimsical energy, fresh color, and pixie-ish characters. His technique begins with “working sketches”, using cut-out sections of text glued to double-sided Strathmore boards, which then become the actual finished artwork. He uses a combination of watercolor, pencil and pen to make most of his illustrations.
Artwork.; Book dummies.; Books.; Children's literature, American--20th century.; Correspondence.; Galley proofs.; Illustrations.; Illustrators, American.; Marketing material.; New York (N.Y.); Notes.; Photocopies.; Photographs.; Proofs.; Sketches.
- Series I: Correspondence and Notes, undated, 1960-2001
  - Algonquin Cat, 1980
    - circa 1980 (Box 10, Folder 173)
    - 1979-1980, 2001 June 23 (Box 10, Folder 174)
      Scope and Contents note
      Includes collection notes from Hilary Knight, 23 Jun 2001.
    - Processing details and receipts (3 items), undated (Box 10, Folder 189)
  - Animal Garden, 2001
    - 14 Jul 2001 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      Includes collection notes from Hilary Knight, 14 Jul 2001.
  - Beginning With Mrs. McBee, 1960
    - 19 Jul 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - A Child's Book of Natural History, Bulk, 1968-1969; 1968-1969, 2001
    - Bulk, 1968-1969, 1968-1969, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      Includes collection notes from Hilary Knight, 23 June 2001.
  - Cricket Magazine, undated, 1974-1991
    - 1974-1991 (Box 17, Folder 292)
    - Packing slips, 1982-1990 (Box 17, Folder 295)
  - Ladybug Magazine, 1992
    - 24 Jun 1992 (Box 17, Folder 293)
  - Matt's Mitt, undated, 1977, 2001
    - undated, 1977, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Telephone Time, 1986
    - 1986 March 5, 1986 October 30 (Box 13, Folder 223)
  - Troll Halloween Books, 1989-1990
    - circa 1989 (Box 11, Folder 200)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 201)
  - Unknown Magazine, undated
    - Accounting sheet, undated (Box 17, Folder 294)
  - When I Was a Little Girl/When I Was a Little Boy, Bulk, 1997-1998; undated, 1997-1998, 2001
    - Bulk, 1997-1998, undated, 1997-1998, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      Includes collection notes from Hilary Knight, July 2001.
- Series II: Published Books Illustrated by Hilary Knight, undated, 1956-2001
  - Algonquin Cat, undated, 1980-2001
    Finished artwork for pp. 13, 18, and 20 given to author Val Schaffner. (see HK notes) Missing artwork: jacket, title page, pp. 2, 4, 34/35, 41, 50, 76/77, 98/99, 103, 105, 107, 115, 118, 130.
    - Separations, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 172)
    - Research (newspaper clippings), undated (Box 10, Folder 175)
    - Research (newspaper clippings), 1980 May-December, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 176)
      Includes collection notes from Hilary Knight, 22 Jun 2001.
    - Research (cards, pamphlets, menu), undated, 1980 February 13, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 177)
      Includes collection notes from Hilary Knight, 2001.
    - Research (photographs), undated, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 178)
    - Sketches (pencil and ink), undated (Box 10, Folder 179)
    - Sketches (pencil), undated (Box 10, Folder 180)
    - Sketches (title page, cover), undated (Box 10, Folder 181)
    - Research (notes on text), undated, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 182)
    - Spot drawings (unused), undated (Box 10, Folder 183)
    - Photocopies of spot drawings, undated (Box 10, Folder 184)
      Used in "Miaow!" show at Nabi Gallery, Aug 31-Sept 17 (1980?). See Nabi Gallery postcard, Box 10, Folder 188.
    - Proof (uncorrected), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - Book jacket proofs, 1980, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 186)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - Artwork (2 items, matted), undated (Box 10, Folder 190)
    - Finished artwork, undated (Box 10, Folder 191)
      Does not include artwork for: jacket, title page, pp. 2, 4, 34, 35, 41, 50, 76, 77, 98, 99, 103, 105, 107, 115, 118, 130.
  - Angie, undated
    Does not include art work for: p. 57.
    - Separations, undated (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Finished artwork, undated (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Finished artwork (cover separations), undated (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Animal Garden, undated
    Does not include artwork for: pp. 1-13, 20, 21, 24-41, 47.
    - Separations, undated (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Book dummy, undated (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Preliminary artwork (unused), undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Finished artwork (for Family Circle Magazine), undated (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Finished artwork (black and white), undated (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Finished artwork (color), undated (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Beginning with Mrs. McBee, undated, 1960
    - Separations, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Preliminary artwork (cover, title page), undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Preliminary artwork, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
      For pp. 8/9, 12/13, 16/17, 20/21, 24/25?, 28/29, 36/37, 40/41, and 44/45.
    - Finished artwork, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Galley (text), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Proofs (text), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Proofs (title page), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - A Child's Book of Natural History, undated, 1969
    - Research- photocopies of Hereford's Primer on Natural History, undated (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Manuscript, 1969 March (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Preliminary artwork, undated (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Book jacket, undated (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Color photocopies, undated (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Finished artwork (p. 15), undated (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Finished artwork (cover), undated (Box 18, Folder 299)
  - Feldman Fieldmouse, undated, 1971
    Does not include artwork for: pp. 1, 39, 44, 52, 58, 65.
    - Separations, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Finished artwork, undated (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Haunted House, undated, 1989-1990
    Does not include artwork for: cover, pp. 6, 7.
    - Separations, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 196)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 11, Folder 202)
    - Page photocopies, undated (Box 11, Folder 205)
    - Finished artwork (cover, pp. 2/3, 4/5, 8/9), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 209)
  - Hilary Knight's Mother Goose, 1993
    - Separations, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 291)
  - Hilary Knight's The Owl and the Pussy Cat, undated
    - Proof (cover), undated (Box 11, Folder 194)
  - I Like it Here, undated
    - Book jacket, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Book jacket (color test), undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Finished artwork (book jacket), undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Jeremiah Octopus, 1962
    - Separations, undated, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Preliminary artwork, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Finished artwork (pp. 2/30), undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Finished artwork (pp. 3/31), undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Finished artwork (p. 4), undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Finished artwork (p. 5), undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Finished artwork (p. 6), undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Finished artwork (p. 7), undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Finished artwork (p. 8), undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Finished artwork (p. 10), undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Finished artwork (p. 11), undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Finished artwork (p. 13), undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Finished artwork (p. 14), undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Finished artwork (p. 15), undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Finished artwork - matted (p. 17), undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Finished artwork (p. 18), undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Finished artwork (p. 19), undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Finished artwork - matted (p. 21), undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Finished artwork (p. 22), undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Finished artwork (p. 23), undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Finished artwork (p. 24), undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Finished artwork (p. 25), undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Finished artwork (p. 26), undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Finished artwork (p. 27), undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Finished artwork (p. 28), undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Finished artwork (p. 29), undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Matt's Mitt, undated, 1975
    Does not include artwork for: cover, p. 20, 21.
    - Separations, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Research (notes and newspaper clippings), undated (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Book dummy (partial), undated (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Book dummy (bound), undated (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Preliminary artwork (pp. 2/3), undated (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Finished artwork, undated (Box 8, Folder 133)
      Does not include cover art work. Art work for pp. 20/21- sent to Marilyn Sachs on March 24 (1975?).
  - Midnight Cat, undated, 1990
    - Separations, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 197)
    - Book layout, undated (Box 11, Folder 204)
    - Page photocopies, undated (Box 11, Folder 206)
    - Finished artwork (pp. 4, 8/9), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 210)
  - Most-of-the-Time Maxie, undated, 1974
    - Separations, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Book dummy, undated (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Preliminary artwork (pp. 6/7), undated (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Finished artwork, undated (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Finished artwork (matted - pp. 28/29), undated (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Proof (bound), undated (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Pettifur, undated, 1977
    Does not include artwork for: cover.
    - Separations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Preliminary artwork (book jacket - unused), undated (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Preliminary artwork (p. 7 - unused), undated (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Finished artwork (p. 7), undated (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Finished artwork (p. 9), undated (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Finished artwork (p. 11), undated (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Finished artwork (pp. 12/13), undated (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Finished artwork (p. 15), undated (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Finished artwork (pp. 16/17), undated (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Finished artwork (p. 19), undated (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Finished artwork (p. 21), undated (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Finished artwork (pp. 22/23), undated (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Finished artwork (p. 25), undated (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Finished artwork (p. 27), undated (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Finished artwork (p. 29), undated (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Finished artwork (p. 31), undated (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Finished artwork (p. 33), undated (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Finished artwork (pp. 34/35), undated (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Finished artwork (p. 37), undated (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Finished artwork (p. 39), undated (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Pumpkin Magic, undated, 1990
    Does not include artwork for: cover, pp. 2, 3, 5.
    - Separations, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 198)
    - Sketches (cover), undated (Box 11, Folder 203)
    - Page photocopies, undated (Box 11, Folder 207)
    - Finished artwork (pp. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6/7, 8/9), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 211)
  - Screamy Mimi, undated, 1981, 1987
    - Separations, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 214)
    - Manuscripts (2 drafts, edited) with letter, undated, 1981 May 22 (Box 12, Folder 215)
    - Book dummy, undated (Box 12, Folder 216)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 12, Folder 217)
    - Preliminary artwork (cover), undated (Box 12, Folder 218)
    - Artwork (with color specifications), undated (Box 12, Folder 219)
    - Artwork (matted), undated (Box 12, Folder 220)
  - A Short Trot With a Cultured Mind, undated
    Does not include artwork for: jacket, pp. 91, 110, 135, 171, 187, and 218.
    - Side by Side: Poems to Read Together, undated, 1998
      - Separations, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 290)
    - Alternate artwork (pp. 124, 218, book jacket), undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Finished artwork, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Six Impossible Things Before Breakfast, undated, 1977
    Does not include artwork for: p. 43.
    - Separations, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 192)
      - When I Have a Little Girl/When I Have a Little Boy, undated, 2001
        - Separations, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
        - Preliminary artwork (color tests), undated, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 64)
        - Preliminary artwork (paper tests), undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
          Inlcudes collection notes from Hilary Knight, 2001.
        - Preliminary artwork (cover), undated (Box 4, Folder 67)
        - Preliminary artwork (color photocopies), undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
        - Finished artwork (part 1), undated, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 72)
          Inlcudes collection notes from Hilary Knight, [2001?].
        - Finished artwork (part 2), undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
        - Proofs (sample typeface), undated (Box 5, Folder 74)
        - Proofs (thumbnails), undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
        - Proofs (complete book), undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Artwork (cover), undated (Box 11, Folder 193)
  - Telephone Time, undated, 1986
    Does not include artwork for: cover, p. 1.
    - Separations, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 222)
    - Manuscripts (2 copies, edited), undated (Box 13, Folder 224)
    - Book dummy, undated (Box 13, Folder 225)
    - Thumbnails, undated (Box 13, Folder 226)
    - Preliminary artwork and sketches, undated (Box 13, Folder 227)
    - Preliminary artwork (cover), undated (Box 13, Folder 228)
    - Finished artwork, undated (Box 13, Folder 229)
      Does not include finished artwork for: cover, p. 1.
    - Cover proof (uncorrected), 14 May 1986 (Box 13, Folder 230)
  - Ten Tall Soldiers, undated, 1991
    Does not include artwork for: cover, pp. 12/13, 36, 38/39.
    - Separations, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 231)
    - Research (photocopies), undated (Box 14, Folder 232)
    - Cover/End papers dummy, undated (Box 14, Folder 233)
    - Preliminary artwork (title page), undated (Box 14, Folder 234)
    - Finished artwork, undated (Box 14, Folder 235)
    - Proofs (cover, title pages), undated (Box 14, Folder 236)
    - Proofs (complete book, 2 copies), undated (Box 14, Folder 237)
    - Proof (complete book), undated (Box 14, Folder 238)
    - Proofs (book jacket, 3 copies), undated (Box 18, Folder 300)
    - Finished artwork (book jacket), undated (Box 18, Folder 302)
  - That Makes Me Mad!, undated, 1976
    - Separations, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 136)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Sketches (pp. 9/10), undated (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Preliminary artwork (cover), undated (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Finished artwork (p. 1), undated, 1976 March 9 (Box 9, Folder 140)
      Includes note from publisher dated March 9, 1976.
    - Finished artwork (p. 4), undated (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - Finished artwork(p. 5), undated (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - Finished artwork (p. 6), undated (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - Finished artwork (p. 7), undated (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - Finished artwork (p. 8), undated (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - Finished artwork (p. 9), undated (Box 9, Folder 146)
    - Finished artwork (p. 10), undated (Box 9, Folder 147)
    - Finished artwork (p. 11), undated (Box 9, Folder 148)
    - Finished artwork (p. 12), undated (Box 9, Folder 149)
    - Finished artwork (p. 13), undated (Box 9, Folder 150)
    - Finished artwork (p. 14), undated (Box 9, Folder 151)
    - Finished artwork (p. 15), undated (Box 9, Folder 152)
    - Finished artwork (p. 16), undated (Box 9, Folder 153)
    - Finished artwork (p. 17), undated (Box 9, Folder 154)
    - Finished artwork (p. 18), undated (Box 9, Folder 155)
    - Finished artwork (p. 19), undated (Box 9, Folder 156)
    - Finished artwork (p. 20), undated (Box 9, Folder 157)
    - Finished artwork (p. 21), undated (Box 9, Folder 158)
    - Finished artwork (p. 22), undated (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - Finished artwork (p. 23), undated (Box 9, Folder 160)
    - Finished artwork (p. 24), undated (Box 9, Folder 161)
    - Finished artwork (p. 25), undated (Box 9, Folder 162)
    - Finished artwork (p. 26), undated (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - Finished artwork (p. 27), undated (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - Finished artwork (p. 28), undated (Box 9, Folder 165)
    - Finished artwork (p. 29), undated (Box 9, Folder 166)
    - Finished artwork (p. 30), undated (Box 9, Folder 167)
    - Finished artwork (p. 31), undated (Box 9, Folder 168)
    - Finished artwork (p. 32), undated (Box 9, Folder 169)
    - Finished artwork (p. 2/3, cover), undated (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Tiger's Chance, undated
    Does not include artwork for: pp. 88, 109, 116, 126, 127.
    - Book jacket, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary artwork (book jacket), undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Finished artwork, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tortoise and Turtle, undated
    Does not include art work for: end papers, title page, pp. 1, 8/9, 22-25, 41-43, 46, 47, 51, 54-59.
    - Preliminary text (pieces), undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Preliminary sketches (pencil), undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Preliminary artwork (book jacket), undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Finished artwork (part 1), undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Finished artwork (part 2), undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Proof (title page), undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Tortoise and Turtle Abroad, undated
    Does not include artwork for: end papers, book jacket, p. 8-11, 14, 15, 18, 19, 21, 49-51.
    - Finished artwork (part 1), undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Finished artwork (part 2), undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Finished artwork (part 3), undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - When I Have a Little Boy, undated, 1967
    - Book dummy (early title: "The Lesson"), undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Separations, undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Separations, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Preliminary artwork (cover), undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Preliminary artwork (cover- alternate title: When I Have a Son), undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Book dummy- alternate title: When I Have a Son, 1967 (Other CLC C1977)
  - When I Have a Little Girl, undated, 2001
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Book dummy, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Softcover book (separated), undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Hardcover book, Danish translation: "Nar jag far en liten flicka" (separated), undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Preliminary artwork (cover), undated, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      Includes notes added by Hilary Knight [2001?]
    - Preliminary artwork (jacket specifications), undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Preliminary artwork (separations), undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Finished artwork (part 1), undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Finished artwork (part 2), undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Witch's Brew, undated, 1990
    Does not include artwork for: cover, pp. 8, 9.
    - Separations, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 199)
    - Page photocopies, undated (Box 11, Folder 208)
    - Finished artwork (pp. 2/3, 4/5, 6, 7), undated (Box 11, Folder 212)
    - Proofs (color), undated (Box 11, Folder 213)
- Series III: Published Articles Illustrated by Hilary Knight, 1973-1997
  - Cricket Magazine, 1973 November - 1997 October
    - Vol. 1: no. 3, 1973 November (Box 15, Folder 241)
    - Vol. 1: no. 4, 1973 December (Box 15, Folder 242)
    - Vol. 1: no. 7, 1974 Mar (Box 15, Folder 243)
    - Vol. 1: no. 9, 1974 May (Box 15, Folder 244)
    - Vol. 2: no. 6, 1975 February (Box 15, Folder 245)
    - Vol. 2: no. 9, 1975 May (Box 15, Folder 246)
    - Vol. 2: no. 9, (matted artwork, 4 items), 1975 May (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Vol. 2: no. 11, 1975 July (Box 15, Folder 247)
    - Vol. 3: no. 6, 1976 February (Box 15, Folder 248)
    - Vol. 3: no. 7, 1976 March (Box 15, Folder 249)
    - Vol. 3: no. 8, 1976 April (Box 15, Folder 250)
    - Vol. 3: no. 10, 1976 June (Box 15, Folder 251)
    - Vol. 3: no. 11, 1976 July (Box 15, Folder 252)
    - Vol. 3: no. 12, 1976 August (Box 15, Folder 253)
    - Vol. 4: no. 2, 1976 October (Box 15, Folder 254)
    - Vol. 4: no. 3, 1976 November (Box 15, Folder 255)
    - Vol. 4: no. 6, 1977 February (Box 15, Folder 256)
    - Vol. 4: no. 7, 1977 March (Box 15, Folder 257)
    - Vol. 4: no. 10, 1977 June (Box 15, Folder 258)
    - Vol. 5: no. 5, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 259)
    - Vol. 5: no. 7, 1978 March (Box 15, Folder 260)
    - Vol. 6: no. 9, 1979 May (Box 15, Folder 261)
    - Vol. 6: no. 10, 1979 June (Box 15, Folder 262)
    - Vol. 7: no. 3, 1979 November (Box 15, Folder 263)
    - Vol. 8: no. 6, 1981 February (Box 15, Folder 264)
    - Vol. 8: no. 10, (scratchboard), 1981 June (Box 15, Folder 265)
    - Vol. 9: no. 9, 1982 May (Box 15, Folder 266)
    - Vol. 11: no. 1, (layout guides), 1983 September (Box 15, Folder 239)
    - Vol. 11: no. 2, 1983 October (Box 16, Folder 267)
    - Vol. 11: no. 10, 1984 June (Box 16, Folder 268)
    - Vol. 11: no. 12, 1984 August (Box 16, Folder 269)
    - Vol. 12: no. 2, 1984 October (Box 16, Folder 270)
    - Vol. 12: no. 7, 1985 March (Box 16, Folder 271)